Hi, everybody. I want to share with you about what's happening to two ranchers in Colorado.
Courtney and Nicole Mallory own 1,000 acres in El Paso County, Colorado.
And despite Nicole being a U.S. military veteran who waves her military flag on their ranch
and being a part of the church community, as well as feeding the residents in El Paso,
from their food, from their ranch, they are being terrorized by locals who want their land.
As seen here in the footage, locals have been jumping the fence.
They have slaughtered their livestock, poisoned their dog, and has driven by their house waving guns.
Nicole was ran off the road when she was coming back from church.
Courtney states that there was a woman that pulled up in his driveway and said that she was supposed to own the land
and made threats about unaliving their dog.
What's worse is that the local sheriff isn't doing anything about it and is being investigated now for being a part of this terrorism.
And they have actually issued a warrant for Courtney and Nicole because of their complaints against the local community and the sheriff.
So they're actually facing criminal charges for reporting everything that's been happening on their land.
So here's my thoughts.
They told us to pull ourselves up by our bootstraps.
They told us to stop using the race card because, you know, racism doesn't exist anymore.
You know, one of the largest lawsuits that ever happened in the United States was against the USDA for discriminating against black farmers.
We know that black farmers make up a very low percent.
I think it's less than two percent of all farmers today.
What racism does, it puts fear in you.
And that's exactly what they're trying to do to Courtney and his wife.
His address has been leaked in a local Facebook group to where now he's in a witness, like a witness protection program.
And this sends shockwaves out.
So now so many other African-Americans are saying, you know what?
I don't want to farm.
I'm scared to go into these areas.
But we can't let fear stop us.
Here's the call to action.
There's a protest that's going to happen at the Denver Capitol coming up.
Pause to read in support of the Karen Act.
As well as numbers to call.